ots.org.pk 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy | OTS

The purpose of this privacy policy is to make a reader aware that how their “Personally Identifiable Information” (PII) is used. PII is information that can be used to identify, contact or locate any single individual. This is according to international privacy standards. Please check our privacy policy carefully to know how we collect, use, protect or handle your “Personally Identifiable Information” according to our website. We care about the protection of your privacy and are dedicated to securing your personal data. 

### Contents:

  1. Who are we?
  2. What data do we collect about you?
  3. Why do we process your personal information?
  4. How will we inform you about changes in our privacy statement?
  5. Your rights
  6. Communication and marketing
  7. How do we protect visitor information?
  8. Who do we share your data with?
  9. Where do we store your data and for how long?
  10. Technical and organizational measures and processing security
  11. Links to third-party websites
  12. Contact
  13. Changes to this Policy

### 1\. Who are we?

Open Testing Service (OTS) is established with the vision to bring innovation in assessment and training process since 2012. OTS is leading by its cost-effective solutions in testing and training sector across the country. We have satisfied clients nationwide and worldwide. Our services include data management, data screening, testing and assessments, training programs; capacity building and enterprise software solutions that help institutions/ organizations improve reliability, increase manpower and educational improvements solutions. We provide a customized service to organizations that want to make over their employment process through assessment with cost-effective and high-quality of standards. 

### 2\. What data do we collect about you?

You will be asked to enter your name, email address, postal address, phone number, qualification or other details while registering on our website in order to use our services as per client or organization requirements. All this information is collected to make a profound data processing, shortlisting for assessment / head hunting to check your eligibility as per our client’s organization requirements. 

### 3\. Why do we process your personal information?

OTS is a service providing company, we provide services to different organizations regarding recruitments and filling vacant posts for both public and private sectors. Your personal data will be used only according to the set policies of the organization. 

We use the following information for the purpose of an ample performance and to improve the services and to protect you from any fraud. 

  * When you enter or provide your data in soft or hard form to OTS.
  * When it is necessary for us to improve our services and to provide you with a protected platform.
  * When there are some legal requirements or our client requirements.
  * Exceptionally we may use your data with your consent, in that case, you will be informed why and where your personal information is going to be used.
  * OTS uses your mobile number, log data and unique device identifiers to protect our platform including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, fraud prevention, system maintenance, support, reporting etc.

### 4\. How will we inform you about changes in our privacy statement?

OTS can change the privacy statement as per requirements. You will be kept informed about these changes through email or you can stay updated from this page. 

### 5\. Your rights

In this section, we will let you know about all those rights you protect while using our services. 

  * **Right to request access:** you are able to access the data and receive a copy to check that if your data is valid.
  * **Right to request correction:** if someone has incomplete or inaccurate data at OTS for some reason. We may add or correct data after verification if required by concern party/authority.
  * **Right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data at any time:** we do not accommodate such cases.

### 6\. Communication and marketing

To confirm your registration an email, SMS or connections with our Services through our website are the primary mediums. However, you may contact us through our helpline. 

### 7\. How do we protect visitor information?

We do not expose scanning against PCI standards. We also do not use Malware Scanning at all. All your personal information is only accessible to the limited number of persons. They have special access rights to certain systems and are bound to keep the information confidential. Moreover, all your sensitive information you provide is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We are implementing a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information in order to maintain the safety of our personal information. All the dealings are processed through an entry provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. 

### 8\. Who do we share your data with?

We do not share or sell your data with third parties. 

### 9\. Where do we store your data and for how long?

We shall be sharing your data for the following purposes through our platform. We do not sell trade or transfer Personally Identifiable Information to any third party unless we inform you with advance notice. Website hosting partners and other parties assisting us in operating our website, conducting our business or serving you are exceptions. All those parties are agreed to keep this information confidential. Your information will be released only if releasing the information is legitimate. Though, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be revealed to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other purposes. We may store data both in soft and hard copy as per our OTS record or data disposal policy. Mostly we dispose of record in hard form after three months of the completion of the project and in the soft form your data is archived. We store all of your data in highly protected warehouses under the surveillance and CCTV cameras. There is a strong access policy where very few of employees are privileged. 

**Test Centers:** OTS may share your data with its test centers which are located across Pakistan. They are working with us providing business operation services as per OTS SOPs. 

**Law enforcement authorities, regulators and others:** OTS may reveal your personal data to any law enforcement authorities, regulators, governmental or public bodies including the third party to obey any legal requirements. 

In case OTS is sold, transferred or merged with some other organization or individual. Your personal data will be used according to the stated privacy policy. 

### 10\. Technical and organizational measures and processing security

In order to provide the best possible user experience, OTS may store and process your data. We shall be holding your personal data for the purpose of any satisfying, legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. If we need to retain the data we will be looking at the nature and sensitivity of that personal data to avoid the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use. You can contact for any queries regarding retention of your personal information at OTS. 

### 11\. Contact

For information and guidance please contact us; 

**Address:** OTS Headquarter (HQ), Office # 01, Central Avenue, Bahria Town, Phase VI, Islamabad.  
**UAN:** 051 111 687 222 (Monday to Saturday From 9:00 AM to 05:30 PM)  
**Fax:** 051-8441353  
**Website:** www.ots.org.pk, **Email:** info@ots.org.pk 

### 12\. Changes to this Policy

The privacy policy may keep changing with the passage of time and within legal requirements. Regular visits to this page will keep you up to date for any changes regarding “Privacy Policies” or you will be notified through email. 

Updated on: 28-01-2019
